How would you survive without your smartphone?
如果没有智能手机，你该如何生活？
For many of us, it’s the gadget we’re most hooked on – looking at it hundreds of times a day.
对我们很多人来说，智能手机是最让我们着迷的设备——每天要看上数百次。
We depend on it to perform a multitude of tasks and to connect with our friends and family.
我们依靠它完成各种各样的任务，以及与亲友保持联系。
But have we become addicted to our phones?
但我们是否已经对手机上瘾了呢？
Certainly, the inventor of the first mobile phone, American engineer Martin Cooper, thinks we might be.
第一部移动电话的发明者、美国工程师马丁·库珀认为我们可能已经上瘾了。
In a BBC interview, he suggested people should stop scrolling and “get a life”.
他在接受BBC采访时建议人们应该停止刷屏，“做点有意义的事情”。
But of course, once we start doom scrolling or watching videos, we just can’t kick the habit.
但当然，一旦我们开始“末日刷屏”或是看视频，就很难戒掉这个习惯。
Psychologist and author Jean Twenge says we’re all guilty of “compulsively checking [our] phone if [we’re] waiting for a text or getting really into social media then kind of, looking up and realising that an hour has passed.”
心理学家兼作家简·特温吉表示，我们都有这样的毛病：“等短信的时候会忍不住频繁查看手机，或者沉迷社交媒体，抬头时才发现一个小时已经过去了。”
There’s even a word – a phubber – to describe a person who ignores the real people around them because they are concentrating on their phones.
甚至还有一个专门的词——“低头族”，用来形容那些因为专注于手机而忽视身边人的人。
But does it matter if we make the most of this technology?
但我们充分利用这项技术，真的有问题吗？
Possibly, because like a drug, the problem arises when it is withdrawn.
或许是有的，因为就像毒品一样，当手机被拿走时，问题就出现了。
A study from King’s College London found young people they studied couldn’t control the amount of time they spend on their phone.
伦敦国王学院的一项研究发现，参与调查的年轻人无法控制自己使用手机的时长。
Such addictive behaviour means that people become ‘panicky’ or ‘upset’ if they are denied constant access, which can cause anxiety and mental health issues.
这种成瘾行为意味着，当人们无法随时使用手机时，会变得“恐慌”或“烦躁”，进而可能引发焦虑和心理健康问题。
Interestingly, another study by the London School of Economics and Political Science suggests we don’t just look at our phones because we are prompted to by a text or email.
有趣的是，另一项由伦敦政治经济学院进行的研究表明，我们看手机不只是因为收到了短信或邮件的提醒。
The people they studied felt automatically urged to interact with their phone, just as a smoker would light a cigarette.
参与研究的人表示，自己会下意识地想要去碰手机，就像吸烟者会习惯性地点烟一样。
Prof Saadi Lahlou, co-author of the study, told the BBC: “We must learn tricks to avoid the temptation when we want to concentrate or have good social relations.”
该研究的合著者萨阿迪·拉卢教授告诉BBC：“当我们想要集中注意力或是维持良好的社交关系时，必须学会一些技巧来抵御这种诱惑。”
One solution could be an app that rewards students for time spent away from their phones.
一种解决办法是开发一款应用，奖励那些放下手机的学生。
Another option is converting your smartphone to a dumbphone that has none of the intoxicating distractions on it.
另一种选择是把智能手机改成功能机，这类手机没有那些让人沉迷的干扰项。
But mainly, perhaps, we just need to look up more and reconnect with the real world!
但或许，最主要的办法还是我们需要多抬头看看，重新与现实世界建立联系！